

Isaac Fimbres

Computer engineering student, currently coursing 7th semester.

- Full-Stack Developer with JavaScript & TypeScript.
- Graphic designer.
- UX/UI designer.

DocumentationMy nationality is mexican, currently I have my mexican passport vigent, and also have a united states Visa for turism.

English: Advanced conversational technician.

Spanish: Native. Italian: Basic limited.

Email: ifimbres@uabc.edu.mx LinkedIn: See my profil

About me

I'm a student of the computer engineering career, specialized in software development. One of my passions is programming, in my leisure time I love to develop my own indie projects of anything that make me curious, like web development or video games development for example.

Currently I started to work as a freelancer in mobile and web development

Education

Fray Junípero Serra High School: In my high school I learn how to use Photoshop and Illustrator to make designs. (2016 - 2018)

Universidad Autónoma de Baja California: Currently I'm coursing 7th semester of my career, I will graduate in december of 2022 and my current GPA is 3.7.

Experience

Task manager with .NET (02/2021 - 06/2021): I have developed a web system that works as a task manager using data bases in MySQL, the back-end is made with C# and ASP.NET Framework, and the front-end is made by HTML5, and CSS, all with Visual Studio. After I finish this project I sell it to a local company here in Ensenada, Baja California.

Mobile game development for Android (12/2020 - 01/2021): Since my 17 years old of age I have developed a couple video games projects in C# with Unity Engine, but the last one I did is the only that I have published, this project is oriented for mobile devices with an Android OS, I made it using pure object oriented C++ code with Unreal Engine, and already is available in the Google App Store, check this

Technologies & languages

Technologies: React, React Native, Express, Mongo DB, Node,

Angular, .NET Framework, MySQL, and Git.

Languages: HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, C#, C++, Python, Assembler, Prolog, C, and Java, but the ones I use the most are Python, JavaScript/TypeScript, and C++.

Software control: Figma, Adobe Creative Cloud, Postman, Workbench, Compass, Robo3T, Unreal Engine, among others.

